listwire.com 2013-06-06

# List Wire Privacy

Internet Marketing Aces, LLC., the parent company of List Wire, is committed to customer service and strives to provide a private and secure browsing experience at our website. The following policy will help you to understand how we treat and use your personal information. As we continue to improve our site and services we may take advantage of developments in technology. When new technology is put in place, this policy is subject to change. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. collects information from our web site in several ways including but not limited to, cookies, sessions, referring websites, website activity, and through data provided by outside services. During registration, Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. asks for some identifying information such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may also be asked for personal information when you report a problem with our site and related services or, if you otherwise contact Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. 

We may require that you provide credit card information, as well as other billing related information when you establish an account with Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. Credit card information is submitted using SSL ( Secure Sockets Layer ), and may be stored offsite on the servers of a PCI Compliant service provider. 

As previously stated Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. collects information using cookies, which are small pieces of data stored by your browser and/or your computer's hard drive. This information allows us to more easily service your account needs and ensure proper tracking of sales in our affiliate referral program. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies unless specifically set not to, use of our website requires cookies. 

Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site, however, we do not store any personal information other than what is necessary to provide proper service. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others for any reason. Information is collected with the sole purpose of providing Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. services. 

When you are on our domain, only Internet Marketing Aces, LLC., its agents and representatives have access to your information. Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. will not disclose any of your personal information except when we have your express permission or under special circumstances, such as when the law requires it. Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. will comply with the requests of all recognized legal entities to aid in the stopping of spam, distribution of illicit sexual content to minors, or any other illegal activity brought to our attention through the proper legal channels. 

Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. may occasionally send you e-mail, contact you via phone, or through postal mail about promotions, service upgrades, and other services that we feel would be of value to your business both with Internet Marketing Aces, LLC., and based on your use of our services. Only Internet Marketing Aces, LLC., or agents or representatives working on behalf of Internet Marketing Aces, LLC., will contact you. 

All leads/contacts/email addresses associated with your account are your property and Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. has no authorization to use them in any way except as instructed by you in accordance with normal account operation. In the event that your account is cancelled for any reason, we will delete any and all contacts in your account within ninety days of account cancellation. 

Your leads/contacts/email addresses are stored in the same database as other account holders, but are stored in such a way that they are kept separate from other account holders. At no time is information about your leads/contacts/email addresses shared with any other subscribers, affiliates or partners unless specifically requested by you, or unless we must provide data in an effort to render a proper decision concerning spam complaints. 

Due to the actions of a given lead/prospect/subscriber, it is possible that other customers of Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. may have duplicate information, or may be reaching the same lead/prospect/subscriber. 

All Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. affiliate information is collected with for the purpose of properly tracking sales for our affiliate referral system. Internet Marketing Aces, LLC. will not sell, share or rent this information to others. 

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites unless they are specifically listed in this privacy policy.
